Can we have the patrol units, particularly west side,
like Lake Mars and areas like that,
just to check boat launches, see if maybe he was
taken back and dropped off in that area,
kind of ride through Lake Mars and other areas,
looking for him.
10-4.
I’m not sure where they looked for him, but if he got
a ride back and got dropped off…
[Follow-up again asks that the area be checked;
several words are unclear.]
A lot of our units checked the boat ramps
in our area,
and Pascagoula checked—there’s negative contact
[with the male] at any boat ramps or piers.
I also contacted Biloxi as well.
They should be calling back shortly.
They’re checking their boat [ramps/routes] as well.